## Yujian 'Charles' Tang

University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill yujian@live.unc.edu • Phone: (919) 741-4667

## **RESEARCH INTERESTS**

My current research topic is on automating the segmentation of subcortical structures in macaque brains using deep learning on a convolutional neural network. Previous research experience includes image processing in neuroimaging, and data cleaning for mobile crowdsensing. Future research interests are in applications of deep learning in data cleaning.

## **EDUCATION**

**University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill (Expected)** B.S., Computer Science

Chapel Hill, NC August 2015-May 2019

Minors: Statistics, Computer Science

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant August 2018-Present

Mentor: Dr. Martin Styner

**Research Experience for Undergraduates, National Science Foundation**Miami, FL

Research Intern May 2018-August 2018

Mentors: Dr. Niki Pissinou, Samia Tasnim

Neuro Image Research and Analysis Labs

Chapel Hill, NC

Research Assistant June 2017-May 2018

Mentors: Dr. Martin Styner, and Sun-Hyung Kim, PhD

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

Department of Computer Science, UNC

Chapel Hill, NC

Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 283) Fall 17, Spring 18, Fall 18

Professor: Dr. David Plaisted

ITS Franklin, UNC Chapel Hill, NC

Middleware Intern June 2017-August 2017

Department of Computer Science, UNC Chapel Hill, NC

Undergraduate Learning Assistant (COMP 410)

Fall 16

Professor: Dr. David Stotts

nCino Wilmington, NC

Developer Intern June 2016-August 2016

**HONORS** 

NC State Math Contest Scholarship Winner, 2015

Undergraduate Learning Assistant of the Year Nominee, 2018

## PRESENTATIONS, PRECEDINGS, AND PAPERS

University of North Carolina Department of Computer Science Research Symposium for Undergraduates, Spring 2018

**LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE** 

Governor of Ram Village
Academic Chair, Pi Alpha Phi Fraternity Inc.

2018-2019
Fall 2018

Lieutenant Governor of Ram Village 2017-2018

Brotherhood, Rush, and Social Chairs, Pi Alpha Phi Fraternity Inc.

Spring 2018